[Music]
from day one we saw exactly what the war
in Ukraine was all about we know exactly
that this is a money grab there is
trillions upon trillions of dollars of
Natural Resources in Western Ukraine we
have pointed that out it's the the wars
that are fought are all about natural
resources and yet there are people the
most disturbing thing John that I have
seen maybe in all the years I've been
following politics is when the
Democratic uh house committee was
standing on the house floor waving the
Ukraine flag I never ever I never see
them wave the American flag and even
that is is jingoistic as it may seem I
could at least understand that but
you're gonna wave the flag of a why
don't you just wave the Israel flag
while you're at
why their office is they have that
hanging all over the place Israel I use
this term very Loosely but president
zalinski had something to say regarding
whether or not we should end the war on
Ukraine on 60 Minutes last night the
risk that Russia will occupy Europe is
100% if the United States pulls out of
NATO Russia will occupy Europe yes so
not all not all the Europe they will
begin from the those countries as I said
who are big our friends but small
countries who've been in the ussi the
Soviet Union they will begin and we'll
see what will be the answer but you so
was that John Bolton or James Clapper
who gave him that talking point John I'm
exactly exactly see this is the thing is
we we so want to believe that we have
independent thinkers making these
foreign policies and we don't there are
no independent thinkers out there it was
you know I I'll tell you a story that
bothers me very much I mentioned it
yesterday on a podcast but I happen to
be Greek Orthodox and um the Orthodox
church has taken a strongly Pro zalinsky
uh position which bothers me very much
and one of the reasons or the primary
reason that that they did this is
because Hillary Clinton when she was the
Secretary of State went to the patriarch
in Constantinople and said we want you
to to recognize the Ukrainian Orthodox
Church as independent of the Russian
Orthodox church it's been a combined
church for a thousand years a little bit
more than a thousand years so uh he said
well the pator said it's not really in
our interest she says I'll give you $15
million state department will transfer
$15 million to the to the Orthodox
Church the patriarch says I'll take the
cash she says but it has to come from
Ukraine so we're going to transfer the
money to the Ukrainian government and
then they'll put it in Ukrainian Banks
and send it to Constantinople well by
the time it got to the patriarch it
wasn't 15 million it was 10 million and
when the patriarch complained to Hillary
Clinton she said I don't know anything
about that all I know is I sent you $15
million and you promis to recognize the
Ukrainian Orthodox Church as independent
which he was forced to but this is year
after year after year Ukraine is on the
United Nations list of the most corrupt
countries on the planet where did we
think our money was going to go did we
think that all of a sudden they were
going to be honest and transparent about
our money of course not and the fix has
been in for what is it now three
years I guess it is so now we're
supposed to be upset that uh that zinsky
doesn't want to settle this he's never
gonna want to settle this everybody's
getting rich I wonder how much real
estate he owns in London by now isn't he
worth like a100 million or something
like that wouldn't be at all surprised
not at all we'll continue Europe will
not answer because they don't have they
will begin to defend itself each country
defend itself and at this
moment so Russia will get all this all
the successes with all the territor they
will want I don't know they will want
30% of Europe 50 I I don't know nobody
knows but they will have this
possibility I just have to say Russia
has a population of like 144 million
people just just physically how do you
propose that Russia occupies Europe just
don't negative population growth
negative doesn't make any it it's just
so implausible it's so bizarre that we
have this idea of uh you know the enemy
of Russia that is so outsized when it
comes to its actual capabilities yeah
not technological right and not you know
like they have been able to hold their
own against you know uh Ukraine backed
backed by NATO right they've done a a
pretty impressive job but the idea of
occupying and holding
all of Europe 30% of Europe what are you
talking about this is no idea
fantasy no look they were I was just
talking with so I was just visiting with
my 90-year-old aunt in Tampa who I
haven't seen in a while and she loves
Rachel Matt app and this is and just
know this is the only woman on the face
of the Earth that gets a pass for me for
that okay so that's that but she truly
believes and I I I try like some of it
she was open to she was actually pretty
open but she truly believes that Putin
is a threat that he wants to take over
Ukraine and I kept trying to say you
know they're not the threat like it's so
brainwashed I'm like you I said to her
I'm like you sound like a mcarthy person
you sound like like it's Red Scare but
it I don't understand they have how many
military bases in the world their
economies is what the size of Spains
what what are we worried about we had
our ships up their ass all the time I
like what if they had their aircraft
carriers in the Gulf of America okay
like would we would we be okay with
that so true it's a it's a bizarre it's
it is a weird bizar world that you step
into well I think it's also a reflection
of the specific type of demographic
we're talking about here uh the people
that buy into the the people that bought
into the Russia gate narrative at the
time I mean anyone with an objective eye
saw without mentioning his name that
there was a member of the DNC who knew
that wasman Schultz was facilitating a
coup against Bernie Sanders behind the
scenes on Hillary Clinton's behalf he
couldn't take it much like Tulsi was not
willing to accept it as the vice chair
of the DNC and he said the hell with
this [__] I'm gonna do something about
it and instead what do they come up with
oh Russia did it what what the [__] does
that even mean and and the fact that
millions of people buy into it that's
the scarier part they don't ask
questions well that's the
problem yeah yeah they're shared of
Putin I've said this a million times why
do we care why do we care what language
our oligarchs speak so for me personally
I don't care if my oligarchs are Arabic
or Chinese or Russian it doesn't really
matter and so it's just hilarious that
they think he's such a bad guy he's
extremely bright so the fact that they
think that he would do something
completely irrational it's like we're so
used to that because our leaders or
morons that I maybe we project that onto
other people but he's pretty bright guy
he's not he knows what his what he can
and cannot do he's not Trump he's not
walking around saying ridiculous
nonsense nobody takes him seriously and
I have a really strong feeling he ain't
bluffing yeah no no I mean I think well
the outcome of the Ukraine war will be
what you know we had people predicting
when it first started is you know Russia
is going to you know they going to want
to keep some of the land that they have
annexed right yeah Ukraine will be left
some you know a rump state of some size
80% of its current size 75% 85% you know
who knows what that negotiation will be
and somehow it'll be like spun as a
victory or I see a little bit less of
that now but before it was you know it
was like the great Forum policy victory
of Ukraine I don't understand in what
world in what world that's been good for
anybody except again for the contractors
who've been sending weapons there well
the bigger problem of course is the
polit the perception politically that
people will look at this from and what I
always have found the most disturbing is
that the people who are the loudest
about whether or not a war should come
to an end are people who would never
pick up a weapon in a million years to
defend this country that has always been
the the greatest indictment on liberal
America as far as I'm concerned because
they're the first ones to say go to war
and then the last ones who would ever
fight and this is even more disturbing
because I don't know what sininsky
thinks he's going to do at this point
because clearly Trump has made it clear
that he wants to end this he he I
totally want my Nobel Prize yeah that's
it he does that's what it's about and so
let me assure you something Donnie we're
gonna get to Israel in a minute you're
not getting anything if you allow this
genocide to continue being facilitated
you're gonna have to do two things so
this is what seninsky had to say
regarding ending this war president
Trump said this week he did not say yes
when he was asked if he sees Ukraine as
an equal member in the peace process he
did say later that Ukraine would have a
seat at the table have you been given
any assurances that Ukraine will have an
equal seat at the negotiating
table so I will never accept any
decisions between the United States and
Russia about Ukraine never and our
people never and our adults and children
and everybody it can't be so this is the
war in Ukraine against us and is our
human losses we're thankful for all the
support Unity between
USA in USA around Ukraine support
bipartisan Unity bipartisan support
we're thankful for all of this but there
is no any leader in the worldall who can
really make a deal with puting without
us about
us hey it's it's at the point of lunacy
at this point as far as I'm concerned
and when you talk about what are we
fighting for you shouldn't have been
fighting anything from the very
beginning and so John I I I would for
for the audience if you could put on
your you know insid or had if you will
uh Boris Johnson gets sent over to K two
weeks after the fighting begins and what
looks like something that was kind of a
warning shot if you will from 's
perspective uh has turned into a
three-year you know stalemate if you
will it could be a hell of a lot worse
but what was the motive of the Prime
Minister of the UK who I have no doubt
was just acting on behalf of the Biden
administration at that time totally
agree I think he was acting on behalf of
the Biden Administration the the
motivation was to drag this war out as
long as it possibly could be dragged out
because every day that there is fighting
we can Russia at least that's the the
consensus here in Washington you want
the Russian economy to collapse you want
Russian soldiers to be killed you want
the Russian population to rise up
against Vladimir Putin because he's
fighting a war that has no end it
weakens Society I've told I've told a
story a thousand times that when I was
with the Senate Foreign Relations
Committee I I went to Afghanistan to
study the heroin poppy crop and uh you
know Afghanistan was producing 93% of of
the world's heroin at the time and I
came back uh to write the paper and I
got a call from DEA they asked if they
could see me so I went out to to see
them and they said look nobody wants
this heroin cultivation to stop because
all that heroin goes to Russia and Iran
and we want their societies to be
weakened well it's exactly the same
thing with the Ukraine war we our policy
is that we want Russia to be weakened we
want their society to be destroyed and
so we can help to affect that by
dragging out this war as long as humanly
possible that's the Democratic party's
uh position on this they were thrown by
Donald Trump's you know we're gonna
we're gonna end this war and and
zilinsky is just playing wrong when he
says that if there's not a seat at the
table for Ukraine that the war can't end
that's [__] the war's going to end
if he's told the war is going to end